celebutopia.net 2013-12-31

# Privacy | Celebutopia

At Celebutopia.net we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it at all times. This Internet Privacy Notice explains how we collect, use, and safeguard information on this Website. Please read this Privacy Notice carefully. By visiting Celebutopia.net, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice and agree that any dispute over privacy is governed by this Privacy Notice and Conditions of Use.

By continuing to use the Celebutopia.net Website after we post any changes to this Privacy Notice, you accept the Privacy Notice as modified.

What Personal Information About Customers Does Celebutopia.net Collect?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at Celebutopia.net. Here are the types of information we collect:

Information You Give Us:  
We receive and store any personal and financial information you enter on our Website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future options for you, improving our Website, and communicating with you.

Automatic Information: 

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Websites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Celebutopia.net, including your IP address. A number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Websites anonymously. Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at Celebutopia.net if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist.

E-mail Communications: 

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Celebutopia.net if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences accordingly.

Will Celebutopia.net sell or share your information?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below.

  * **Third-Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Celebutopia.net or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

  * **Protection of Celebutopia.net and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Celebutopia.net, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.

  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**Conditions Of Use, Notices, And Revisions**

By visiting Celebutopia.net, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of California. If you have any concern about privacy at Celebutopia.net, please do not hesitate to contact us.  

**Behavioral Targeting  
**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)
